policyx.com 2019-09-29

# Privacy Policy | PolicyX

PolicyX.com Insurance Web Aggregator Private Limited, we are committed to protecting your privacy as a visitor to this Web site and as our customer. We will not disclose trade, transmit, transfer, share, sell, disseminate, lease or rent any personally identifiable information to any third party except our affiliate partners/ insurance providers. We encourage you to read the following Privacy Statement that contains information regarding the collection, use, disclosure, and protection of your information.

## Using Information Gathering

When you enroll for an insurance policy at PolicyX.com Insurance Web Aggregator Private Limited, we will ask you to provide your name, home address, mailing address, telephone number, and e-mail address. This information will be provided to the insurance company when you purchase an insurance policy so they can establish you as a policyholder. By applying here you authorize us and our associate partners to call and/or SMS you notwithstanding your registration with NDNC.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on a visitor's hard drive while they are visiting this Web site. We may utilize a short-lived form of cookie when you visit this site. At PolicyX.com cookie is only used to identify one unique visitor from another visitor during a particular session. A session is the period of active site-use while that unique visitor is linked to our server. We may use cookie technology during a session as a tool to carry forward your input information during the enrollment process. This enables the visitor to input their information once and have the information appear later during the enrollment process. No personally identifiable information is stored on the cookie. The cookie expires and is deleted from the visitor's computer as soon as they close their browser or if they are not actively browsing our Web site for more than 20 minutes. 

## Third Party Links

This Web site may contain links to third-party Web sites that are not controlled by PolicyX.com. These third party links are made available to you as a convenience and you agree to use these links at your own risk. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content of third party Web sites neither linked to us nor are we responsible for the privacy policy or practices of third party Web sites linked to PolicyX.com. Our Privacy Policy only applies to information we collect from you while you are at PolicyX.com. If you should link to a third party Web site from PolicyX.com we strongly encourage you to review and become familiar with that Web site's privacy policy.

## Legal

We pertinaciously follow the norms of the non-disclosure agreement. We may disclose any personal information if required or permitted to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal process served on us or otherwise comply with the law. PolicyX.com ensures that the websites linked to us are safe and secure. However, we have no control over 3rd party websites.

## Changes In Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without publishing an advance notice of our intent to make the changes. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at helpdesk@policyx.com
